*我就喜欢一个人住*
*I love to live alone*
*可以随意打扫卫生*
*'cause I'm in my cleaning zone*
加比  你好
Gabi, hi!
你怎么样  瑞士好不好
How are you? How's Switzerland?
源自瑞士阿尔卑斯山区的唱法
你学会唱约德尔调了吗
Have you learned how to yodel yet?
你每个星期都要问我一次
You ask me that every week
而答案仍然是  木有嘞哦嘞
and the answer is still no-de-lay-hee-hoo!
每次都戳到我笑点
Gets me every time.
等会儿  今天又不是礼拜天晚上
Wait a minute. It's not Sunday night.
你为什么现在跟我视频
Why are you calling me now?
我就是想你了
I just missed ya.
法式料理  在食物上浇烈酒并点火
火焰烧之周过得怎么样
How did flambe week go?
太热辣了
Fla-mazing.
我学会了怎么用白兰地做黑椒牛排
I learned how to make a peppercorn steak with brandy,
怎么烧毁餐厅
how to burn down a restaurant,
怎么做橘子黄油薄饼
how to make Crepe Suzette...
等会儿  倒回去一点
Wait, wait. Back up.
秘诀就在于柠檬皮屑
So, the secret is actually lemon zest...
再多倒一点
Back it up a little more.
我好像听见了烧毁餐厅什么的
Something about burning a restaurant down?
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
是啊  起了一丁丁点的大火啦
Yeah. There may have been a teeny-tiny major fire.
我用的法国酒度数
The French alcohol that I was using
翻译   啾啾    妖精希亚
比我想象的高了一点
was a little higher proof than I realized.
都怪欧洲人用公制
I blame the metric system.
翻译  roaddog
别人也这么觉得吗
Did they?
不  他们怪我
No, they blamed me.
校对  roaddog
好可怜  你打算怎么办
Oh, you poor thing. What are you gonna do?
回家呗
Come home?
时间轴 aaaBao
天啊  你回来了
Oh, my god! You're here!
他们把我赶走了
They kicked me out.
后期 斯人  总监 roaddog
你还好吗
Aw, you okay?
不好嘞哦嘞
No-de-lay-hee-hoo!
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
饥饿的青春
第二季  第十一集
总体来说  你还玩得挺爽的
Well, overall, it sounds like you had a great time.
但你觉得我们
But don't you think
是不是应该谈谈最明显的问题
we should talk about the elephant in the room?
是的  索菲亚  我会找到工作
Yes, Sofia, listen, I'm going to get a job
然后就可以付房租了
and I'm going to be able to pay rent.
-我保证  -不  我说的是乔什
- I promise. - No, I was talking about Josh.
这个问题啊
Oh, that elephant.
那你打算怎么办
So, what's your plan?
幸亏你问起
It's funny you should ask.
我本来打算直接从机场去他家
I was gonna go to his place straight from the airport,
望着他的眼睛  说
I was going to look him right in the eye and say,
"我当时就那么走了  真是很残酷无情
"The way that I left was hurtful and horrible
非常非常抱歉
and I am so, so sorry.
你能不能原谅我"
Can you ever forgive me?"
-你怎么没说  -我好怕怕
- Well, why didn't you? - I got scared.
我在瑞士的时候  试过联系他
When I was in Switzerland, I tried reaching out.
给他打了电话  还发了短信
I called him and I texted him.
但后来又觉得好像不该烦他
But then I felt like I should just leave him alone.
-为什么  -因为他回我说"别烦我"
-Why? -'Cause he wrote back, "Leave me alone."
但现在我回家了  很想见他
But now that I'm home, I really want to see him.
为什么  因为你觉得内疚
But why? Because you feel guilty?
还是你想道歉
Because you want to apologize?
还是你仍然喜欢他
You still have feelings for him?
是  是  我也不知道
Yes, yes, and I don't know.
天啊
Oh, my god!
你觉得我是不是下意识地烧了餐厅
Do you think that I subconsciously burnt down that restaurant
好早点回来见他
so that I could come home early and see him?
当然不是
No!
你对警察和其他人也得这么说
And that is what you will tell the police and everyone.
我真不敢相信
I still can't believe
你能用手机控制它
you're controlling that with your phone.
是啊  我的应用
Yeah. With my app,
可以用任何一部手机遥控无人机
you can control it with any phone.
就好像是个万能电视遥控器
It's kind of like a universal TV remote,
不过遥控的是无人机
but for drones.
两件人人都爱的事
Two things that everyone loves.
无人机和一直拿着手机
Drones and people always on their phones.
我要买
I want to buy it.
跟你说过了  这个应用不卖的
Like I told you before, the app isn't for sale.
那我说点新鲜的吧
Well, here's something new.
我买了你的整个公司如何
How about I buy your whole company?
没兴趣
Not interested.
-我出价五亿美元  -太感兴趣了
- I'll give you half a billion dollars. - Interested.
尤兰达  如果乔什把公司卖给卡尔
Yolanda, if Josh sells his company to Kal,
那我就会是
I will be the publicist
旧金山富豪之一的公关啦
to one of the richest men in San Francisco.
而我就要给
And I'll be washing the underpants
旧金山富豪之一洗内裤啦
of one of the richest men in San Francisco.
还是你的比较好听
Yours sounds better.
乔什会卖个好价钱的
Josh is about to hit it big
他的整个团队都会跟着沾光
and his whole team will share the glory.
除了你
Except you.
你是新来的
You're new.
没人在乎你
No one cares about you.
谁伤害你了
Who hurt you?
我去开门  今天是最美好的日子
I'll get it! This is the best day ever.
你好
Hi!
天啊  它回来了
Oh, my god! It returned!
走开
Go away!
快开门  艾略特
Please, Elliot.
我只是想和乔什谈谈
I just need to talk to Josh.
不行  你再也不许进这个门了
No! You will never set foot in this house again...
神啊  加比  快进来
Oh, my damn, Gabi! Come on in!
不行  尤兰达  我不允许
No, Yolanda! I forbid it.
不你个头
Forbid this.
-加比  -你好  乔什
- Gabi? - Hey, Josh.
是我觉得  还是气氛真的变尴尬了
Is it me or did it just get awkward in here?
你早回来了
You're back early.
是啊  这个...
Yeah, about that.
听着  我有事想和你谈谈
Listen, I kinda wanted to talk to you about something.
艾略特  我们或许不该在这儿看着
Elliot, maybe we shouldn't stand here and watch this.
说得对  我们挪那儿去吧
You're right. Let's stand over there.
如果你是想要回工作
If this is about your job,
我已经雇了个新的厨师
I actually hired a new chef.
是啊  我知道  尤兰达告诉我了
Yeah, I know, Yolanda told me.
就是她  阿德里亚娜
Here she is. Adriana.
这位是加比  我的前任...厨师
This is Gabi, my ex-- chef--
前任厨师
ex-chef.
你就是加比
Oh, you're Gabi.
或者是艾略特说的
Or as Elliot calls you,
"那个连名字都不能提的人"
"She who must not be named."
-很高兴认识你  -很高兴
- Pleased to meet you. - Very nice to meet you.
现在是不是可以...
So, is now a good time for us to--
不行  他不想跟你谈
Never! He doesn't want to talk to you!
真的吗乔什  你不想跟我谈吗
Is that true, Josh? Do you not want to talk to me?
他当然想跟你谈
Of course he wants to talk to you!
他有一肚子话想对你说
He's got a lot of feelings he needs to let out!
我也有一肚子话想对你说
Because I have feelings that I need to let out, too.
第一句就是  对不起
Starting with I'm sorry.
省省你的道歉吧  他已经翻篇了
You can save your apology! He has moved on!
翻篇个鬼
The hell he has!
尤兰达  别多管闲事
Yolanda, stay out of it!
停
Stop!
你  你  出去
You! You! Out!
有人被戳到痛处了
Someone's wound a little tight!
艾略特说得对
Look, Elliot's right.
你没必要跟我道歉
You don't need to apologize to me.
我已经翻篇了  我很好
I've moved on. Everything's cool.
别误会  吃你甜点的是只海鸥  不是我
In case you were wondering, a seagull ate your dessert, not me.
我该走了
I better be off.
卡尔  这是我的前任厨师加比
Kal, this is my former chef Gabi.
她刚从瑞士
She just got back
一个很棒的培训班学成归来
from a really fancy apprenticeship in Switzerland.
欧洲的培训班  你一定很厉害
Ooh, an apprenticeship in Europe. You must be good.
我正想招一个厨师  你有兴趣吗
I'm looking for a chef. Are you interested?
-你说什么  -你说什么
- Excuse me? - Excuse me?
对不起  我们还没正式介绍
I'm sorry. We haven't been properly introduced.
我刚搬到隔壁  我叫卡尔  是个亿万富翁
I just moved in next door. I'm Kal. I'm a billionaire.
隔壁吗
Next door?
听着乔什  我不想让你
Listen, Josh, the last thing I want to do
觉得太尴尬
is make you feel awkward.
啥  我  不  你  尴尬  我  怎么会
What? Me? No. You! Awkward! Me? What?
她走之前我们有点小误会
Look, we had a little thing before she left.
实际上也没什么事  差不多而已
Actually, we didn't. We almost did.
我可不想掺合进什么事里
Well, I really don't want to get into the middle of a thing.
没事  你没听我说吗
There was no thing. Did you not just hear me?
什么事都没有
No thing happened.
既然没什么事
And since there was no thing,
也就没什么掺合不掺合的
there's nothing to get in the middle of.
全都是...浮云
Just a bunch of-- air.
那你不介意我接受这工作吧
So, you're cool if I take the job?
介意  我  什么  当然不  工作  接吧
Cool! Me! What? Yes! Cool! Me! Yeah! Job. Take.
-你确定吗  -到底有没有人在听我说话
- You're sure? - I mean, is no one hearing what I'm saying?
话筒没开吗  接吧
Is this thing on? Take the job.
好吧  那我接受  谢谢你
Okay. I guess I'll take it. Thank you.
太好了  你可以立即上岗吗
Great! Can you start right away?
我明晚有个非常重要的商务晚宴
I've got a very important business dinner tomorrow night,
必须要能打动对方
and I really have to impress the guy.
那人是谁
Oh, who's the guy?
在下
Me.
我还是不敢相信
I still can't believe it.
只有你能找到
Only you would get a job
正好在"问题"家对面的工作
that just so happens to be across the hall from the elephant.
我知道  但是我问了他一百次
I know! But I asked the elephant a hundred times
他都说不介意
and he said he was cool with it.
我该怎么办  我需要一份工作
So what am I supposed to do? I need a job.
既然那样  请坐
Well, on that note, take a seat.
索菲亚  我不需要你打鸡血
Sofia, I don't need one of your pep talks
那跟听讲座没啥区别
that's actually a lecture.
但是你真的需要
Oh! But you do.
这个新工作是个崭新的开始
This new job is a fresh start.
为了保证你步入正轨
So, to help you stay on track,
我整理了一张《要和不要做》清单
I've put together a little list of "dos and don'ts".
"要表现得专业
"Do act professional.
不要跟你老板上床
"Don't have sex with your boss.
要穿裤子
"Do wear pants.
不要脱下来"
Don't take them off."
索菲亚  我没有要跟...
Sofia, I'm not gonna sleep with--
"要为卡尔和乔什准备美味的晚餐
"Do prepare a delicious dinner tonight for Kal and Josh.
不要跟乔什订婚  不要看他
"Don't engage with Josh. Don't look at him.
不要谈论过去  不要谈论未来"
Don't talk about the past. Don't talk about the future."
-那如果...  -不要
- But what if-- - Don't.
-那如果他...  -不要
- But what if he-- - Don't.
好吧  你说得对  索菲亚
Okay, fine. You're right, Sofia.
没有你我在瑞士是怎么挺过来的啊
Man, how did I ever make it in switzerland without you?
你没挺过来
You didn't.
你烧了一间餐厅
You burned down a restaurant.
天呐  加比  这太不可思议了
Oh, my god. Gabi, this looks amazing.
你这本来装修就很好
Well, your place is amazing.
我特别喜欢那架钢琴
I especially love the piano.
-是三角钢琴吗  -它可不止三角钱
- Is it a grand? - Oh, it cost way more than that.
卡尔  我想让你知道
Listen, Kal, I just want you to know
今晚跟乔什的晚餐
that tonight's dinner with Josh
会非常的专业
is going to be completely professional.
-为什么会不专业  -不会的
- Why wouldn't it be? - It would be.
乔什来了
That's Josh.
我要去里屋等着
I'm going to go in the other room.
你一会能像《唐顿庄园》里那样介绍我吗
Could you announce me how they do on Downton Abbey?
可以
Yes.
好了  专业一点  不谈过去
Okay. Be professional. Don't talk about the past.
不谈未来
Don't talk about the future.
我们谈谈吧
We need to talk.
加比  今晚真的很重要
Gabi, this is a really important night.
我知道  对我来说也是
I know! For me, too!
我们终于有机会谈谈了
We finally have a chance to talk.
我要跟卡尔谈生意
I'm talking about the deal with Kal.
这个对我真的很重要
This is really important to me.
但我知道你对我有感情
But I know that you're feeling things.
比如...讨厌吗
Like annoyed?
对  很好  继续
Good. That's good. Go on.
我昨天说的都是真心话
Look, I meant what I said yesterday.
你在这工作我不介意
I'm cool with you working here,
所以你能不能表现得专业一点
so can you please just act professional?
好吧  您要喝酒吗  先生
Fine! Can I get you a glass of wine, sir?
不  谢谢  五亿美元的生意可得谨慎
No, thank you. $500 million deals and alcohol do not mix well.
我本来想等你介绍
I was waiting to be announced,
但一个男人又能躲在门后多久呢
but how long can a man hide behind his own door?
抱歉  现在有请...
Sorry. May I please introduce--
时机已经过了
The moment passed.
-你好  乔什  -你好  卡尔
- Hello, Josh. - Good to see you, Kal.
开始之前
Before we get started,
我有件私事想和你讨论下
there's something personal I wanted to discuss with you.
好的  什么事
Sure, what is it?
我就直说了
All right. I'll get right down to it.
我对你的厨师有意思
I'm hot for your chef.
希望你不介意
I hope it's not a problem.
介意吗
Problem?
才不介意  多好
Hell no, it's great!
她太棒了
She's fantastic.
我知道我们才认识
I know we only just met,
但真的特别有默契
But we've got the most amazing connection.
很好  这消息真有趣
I love it! It's fun. Fun news.
好  等吃完晚餐
Great! I'm going to ask her out
我就准备约她出去
as soon as we're finished with dinner.
好  头盘准备好了
Okay, the first course is ready.
看起来真美味
This looks divine.
加比  你真是上帝的恩赐
Gabi, you're a godsend.
难以置信你居然让我挖走她
I can't believe you let me steal her away from you.
她已经没替我工作了  不算挖
It's not stealing when she wasn't even working for me.
加比  再倒点酒
Gabi, more wine?
-我以为你...  -倒
- Oh, I thought you-- - More wine!
该词暗指女性私处
加比  你的生蚝太完美了
Gabi, your oyster is perfection.
真高兴你喜欢
I'm so glad you like it.
还有很多呢
There's plenty more where that came from.
够了  你猜怎么着  我不用吃这顿大餐
All right! You know what? I don't need this big fancy dinner.
我也吃过加比的生蚝
I've had Gabi's oysters.
把初始报价合同给我签字吧
Do you have the initial offer for me to sign?
目的很明确哈
A man who knows what he wants.
好  我们来谈生意
All right. Let's get down to biz-natch.
你可以仔细看下合同...
Now feel free to take your time and look over--
不用  废话废话  一堆零
No. Blah, blah, blah. Lots of zeros.
看起来不错  签字了
All looks in order. Signing.
意向书送给律师过目
Letter of intent off to the attorney's.
很高兴和你做生意
Great doing biz-natch with you.
再见  拜拜  我走了
Cheerio! Tut-tut! Must be off!
下面呈上第二道...
May I now introduce the second course--
你根本没看过《唐顿庄园》  是不是
You've never seen Downton Abbey, have you?
是的
No.
我今晚准备约她出去
I'm going to ask her to hang out tonight.
卡尔  你猜怎么着
Hey, Kal, guess what?
我不在乎
I don't care!
香槟  好像这能打动她一样
Champagne! Like that's going to impress her.
妈呀  还真有用
Holy cow, I think it did!
这就去卧室  太快了吧
Is it too soon to go to the bedroom?
不
No!
等等  阿德里亚娜吗
Wait! Adriana?
不  不要  不要
Oh, no! No, no, no! No, no, no!
坠毁  无人机坠毁了
Ohh, drone down! We have a drone down!
谢谢
Thank you!
第一天怎么样
Good first day?
你会很满意的  我没脱裤子
You' will be happy to know, I kept my pants on.
敬你的循序渐进
Here's to baby steps.
卡尔人很好  我们很融洽
Kal was great. I had no problem with Kal.
但乔什来参加商务晚宴时
But when Josh showed up for his business dinner,
不愿跟我说话
he wouldn't talk to me.
我想让他跟我谈谈  他就是不干
I tried to get him to talk to me, but he just wouldn't.
然后说"拜拜  再见  我走了"
And then he was all like, "Tut-tut. Cheerio. I must be off".
你干嘛那样看着我
Why are you looking at me like that?
就是你这愚蠢  爱演的样子
It's just-- all your stupid, crazy, drama--
我好想你
I missed you!
我不是光愚蠢又爱演的
Come on. I'm not all stupid, crazy drama.
加比  快开门  加比
Gabi, open the door quick! Gabi! Gabi! Gabi!
我把无人机飞进卡尔家里  现在坠毁了
I flew a drone into Kal's penthouse and I crashed it
需要你去帮我拿回来
and I need you to get it back for me.
不敢相信我还觉得学织毛衣就不空虚了
I can't believe I thought learning to knit could fill this void.
好吧  你在说什么
Okay, what are you talking about?
加比  我需要你去把那架无人机拿回来
Look, gabi, I need you to get that drone back for me.
我会损失五个亿的
I could lose $500 million.
-好吧  我帮你  -太好了  我们走
- Okay, I'll help you. - Great. Let's go.
如果...
If--
如果你同意拿回来以后谈谈
if you agree to have a talk when we're done.
情真意切地谈谈
A real talk. A feelings talk.
-你有卡尔家钥匙吗  -有
- Do you have the key to Kal's apartment? - Yes.
那就情真意切地谈谈  走
Feelings talk it is. Let's go.
无人机应该在钢琴边上
I think the drone is over by the piano.
好  等一下
Okay. Wait here.
乔什  找到了
Josh, I got it.
那是地宝
That's a roomba.
吸尘器
A vacuum.
现在是告诉你的时候了
Now would be a good time to tell you,
我不知道无人机长什么样
I don't know what a drone looks like.
是带四个螺旋桨的小飞机
It's a quad copter with four rotors.
四个螺旋桨啊  你不早说
Four rotors! Why didn't you say so?
什么声音  卡尔
What the hell? Kal!
我怎么会在这里
What-- what am I doing in here?
你可能想这么问吧
Is the question you're probably asking.
加比  我知道你在找乔什的无人机
Gabi, I know you're looking for Josh's drone.
无人机长这样啊
Oh, that's a drone!
被你抓住了  我是来找这个的
Yep, you caught me. That's what I'm here for.
但不是因为他让我来的
But not because he put me up to it.
我是一个人...和乔什来的
I'm here completely on my own-- with Josh.
乔什  你们在我家里搞什么
Josh, what the hell is this doing in my apartment?
卡尔  听我解释
Kal, I can explain everything.
这无人机的人工智能技术太先进了
The drone's artificial intelligence is too advanced.
或许是机器人起义的开端
This could be the start of a robot uprising.
别乱扯  你为什么要监视我
Cut the crap. Why are you spying on me?
卡尔  我不是在监视你
Kal, I'm not spying on you.
外面怎么回事
What's going on out here?
阿德里亚娜
Adriana?
该问的是你穿着那性感睡袍怎么回事吧
I think the question is what's going on in there, sexy robe?
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
我就知道你介意我跟你厨师约会
I knew you were bothered when I asked if I could date your chef.
你在监视阿德里亚娜
You were spying on Adriana.
等等  卡尔  你问乔什能不能跟他厨师约会
Wait, Kal, you asked Josh if you could date his chef?
你以为他说的是我  不是她吗
Did you think he meant me chef and not she chef?
什么
What?
我知道怎么回事了  他没有监视你
I know what's going on here. Listen, he wasn't spying on you.
是在监视我
He was spying on me.
我不在乎他监视谁
I don't care who he was spying on.
重点是他监视人
The point is he was spying!
我要信任自己合作的人
I need to trust the people that I work with.
生意吹了  你被解雇了
The deal is off. And you, you're fired.
-什么  -什么
- What?  - What?
但你还说我的生蚝很完美
But what about my perfect oyster?
那谁来帮你做饭
But who's gonna cook for you?
实际上  我准备来
Actually, I'm going to.
乔什  对不起  我辞职了
Josh, I'm sorry, I quit.
现在准备为卡尔工作
I'm going to go work for Kal now.
等等  你要替跟你上床的人
Wait a minute. You're going to cook for the same guy
工作吗
you're sleeping with?
姑娘  我可有张清单要送你
Girl, I have a dos and don'ts list for you.
真是多谢  你让我被解雇了
Well, thanks a lot, you just got me fired!
是啊  你还砸了我五亿美元的生意呢
Yeah, well, you just cost me a $500 million deal!
我吗  分明是你自己
Me? Me? That was you.
-都怪你  -随便了
- That was all you! - Oh, whatever!
行了  我们说好的  该谈谈了
Okay. Deal's a deal. Time to talk.
好  我很伤心
Okay. I'm upset.
我的无人机碎了  你还知道了我的感受
I think my drone's broken. And now you know how I feel.
你到底是怎么回事
What the hell is the matter with you?
我才回来时  你说你放下了  不介意了
When I first got back, you said you'd moved on. You were good.
现在  突然又开始监视我
And now, all of a sudden you're spying on me
因为觉得我在和你邻居上床
because you think I'm sleeping with your neighbor?
这都是怎么回事
What is that all about?
你真想知道这都是怎么回事吗
Do you really want to know what that's all about
还是又准备一遇到难题
or are you just gonna jump on another plane
就坐飞机跑路
when things get too difficult?
所以你是在生气
So you are mad.
你把我一个人晾在这  加比
You pulled the rug out from under me, Gabi!
让我在艾略特的订婚派对上像个傻子
You left me like a smiling idiot at Elliot's engagement party!
我跟你说了爱你  吻了你
I told you I loved you, I kissed you,
我也知道这对你有意义
and I know that meant something to you.
-是的  -那你为什么还让我那样
- It did. - Then why would you leave me like that?
因为...
Because--
乔什  如果我看到你  就走不掉了
Josh, if I saw you then I wouldn't have been able to go.
第一次离开时  我一直扪心自问
When I first left, I kept asking myself
怎么才要在一起了我就要走
how I could leave when we were just getting started.
那你问出什么了
And what did you come up with?
因为我可什么理由都想不到
Because I couldn't come up with anything.
跟你在一起太简单了
Being with you would have been too easy.
现在这样简单吗
This is easy?
乔什
Josh.
为哄我高兴你可以移山开路
You would move mountains to make me happy.
但我想自己移山  你懂我的意思吗
And I want to move my own mountains. Does that make any sense?
我知道山是什么
I know what mountains are.
我去瑞士  是因为想做下一个茱莉亚·蔡尔德
I went to Switzerland because I want to be the next Julia Child.
如果你什么事都帮我做了
And if you did everything for me,
那我就失去了实现梦想的动力
then I would lose my own drive to make that dream come true.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
我知道梦想是什么
I know what dreams are.
乔什
Josh...
加比
Look, Gabi--
你离开以后  事情很糟
when you left, it was horrible.
我不知所措
I was a mess.
所以全心投入工作
So I threw myself into work--
然后...实际上差点做成了
and-- actually it kinda got me to a place
五亿美元的大生意
where I almost made $500 million.
所以  我离开是好事吗
So, me leaving was a good thing?
没错  我的会计师觉得你该多毁掉我的生活
Yeah. My accountant thinks you should ruin my life more often.
但是...加比
But, Gabi...
我不能再经历这事了
I can't go through that again.
乔什  对不起  真的真的对不起
Josh, I am sorry. I am really, truly, very, very sorry.
你会原...
And you for...
我原谅你  加比
I forgive you, Gabi.
乔什  你不用这么大度的
Josh, you did not have to say that.
那我们现在怎么办
So, where do we go from here?
不如做回我们最擅长的事吧
How about we go back to doing what we do best?
-朋友  -我很赞成
- Being friends. - I would love that.
我也是
Me, too.
-那我们没事了吗  -没事了
- So, we're good? - We're very good.
好了  情真意切的谈话结束
Good. Feelings talk adjourned.
我走了
All right. I got to get out of here.
还要早起去找工作呢
I gotta get up early and start the job search.
天啊  天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
天什么呀
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. What?
不敢相信我居然要说这话
I can't believe I'm about to say this.
什么
What?
-你想...  -想
- Do you want... - Yes!
-继续干吗  -想
- ...your old job back? - Yes!
我想  谢谢  谢谢
Yes, I do, thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
现在我就不用早起啦
Now I don't have to get up early.
谢谢你情真意切的谈话
Thanks for the feelings talk.
这不就是朋友该干的嘛
What are friends for?
-明天见  大厨  -明天见  老板
- See you tomorrow, chef. - See you tomorrow, boss.
艾略特  我有事要说
Elliot, I have some news.
和卡尔的交易泡汤了
The deal with Kal's off.
讨厌  那么多钱呢
Damn it! All that money!
好吧  那我就只当
Okay, well, I'll just be the publicist
旧金山帅哥之一的公关好了
to another cutest guy in San Francisco.
还有些别的事...
I have some other news--
阿德里亚娜辞职了
Adriana quit.
-早上好  -不要啊
- Good morning. - No!
它还活着  不要
It lives! No!